Students, your midterm examinations
will take place the week after next.
There are four subjects total,
and Stellas will be rewarded
UNCLE THE PRIVATE TUTOR
for the top two scoring students
for each subject in each grade.
On the other hand, those who receive
failing marks will receive a Tonitrus Bolt,
so bear this in mind.
I will now return your history
quizzes from the other day.
Alice Paulette.
Don't tests make you nervous, Anya?
Edward Perkshire.
No problem.
I've been studying hard lately.
Anya Forger.
Not elegant. You will have a
supplementary lesson after school.
Heh.
That is a flawless impression, Lord Damian!
You got how stupid she looks down perfectly.
I hate Second Son, but I just had a great idea.
Supplementary Lesson
If I read Second Son's mind during
history exams, I can get good scores.
Forger! What are you laughing about?
As punishment, you get an extra assignment.
The teacher was mean,
and now I'm getting home late.
Mister Moon is peeking out to say hello.
Papa! Papa!
Welcome home.
What are you so panicked about?
Papa, how much of Mister Moon
will be out in two weeks?
Oh, you mean the lunar phase?
In about two weeks, it'll be the new moon.
Were you going to go stargazing?
I knew it!
By the way, you have your exams
in two weeks, don't you?
All right, then. Let's do
some studying before dinner.
I'll go over any parts you don't understand.
Hello? Let's start studying.
Anya, the super telepath
who saved the world...
Even Anya has her weaknesses.
The guys at the lab called
it "eclipse" or something.
On the one day each month
that Mister Moon goes away,
Anya's power to read minds goes away, too.
The tests are on the day of the eclipse.
Which means Anya...
won't be able to cheat on the tests!
Oh, no... I'm facing my
biggest challenge ever.
I know! Bond, look into the future
and show me the test answers!
Hamburg steak!
Tonight we're having Papa's
Hamburg steak for dinner!
Yay!
I'm surprised you knew.
Did you peek in the fridge?
I guess we can start dinner.
Om nom...
Zzz...
What am I going to do about
my tests?! I totally passed out!
That's why I suggested
that we study yesterday.
I'm off today, so I'll spend
the whole day helping you out.
Her midterms will cover four subjects.
Which also means that she can receive
up to four Tonitrus Bolts at once.
I've long since given up on the possibility
of her getting four Stellas.
Combined with her finals, it is very possible
she will receive a total of eight Tonitrus Bolts.
I need to make sure she doesn't get expelled
before I sneak into that social gathering.
To prevent that, we need to raise
her basic academic knowledge.
So this obviously becomes this...
And then, that'll lead to
the social gathering...
Papa's mind is talking so much that
I can't concentrate on studying.
Hmm... I still can't figure out
what's so hard for her.
Oh, right. I asked Yuri if he would
be Miss Anya's tutor the other day,
and he seemed rather optimistic about it.
Should I give him a call?
Is that all right?
Unkie!
Yahoo-hoo! I'm here, Sis!
So fast...
Welcome, Yuri.
It's been a while, Yuri.
Maybe we should permanently leave
out the happy married couple set.
Grr! What are you doing here, Loid Forger?
Go to work on your day off, too.
This is my younger brother Yuri, Miss Anya.
So this imp is the child
of the accursed Forger.
I am Papa's child, Anya.
Peased to meet you.
Secret Police? Is he scary?
Sis is basically a goddess!
Sis's outfit is so stylish
I miss Sis's cooking
I get to see Sis today. What a blessed day!
Sis was dazzling the other day
and she's still dazzling today!
Sis!
Maybe I'll kill Loid Forger and take Sis back
I was about to die from loneliness since I hadn't seen Sis in a week
Sis looks great with a kid next to her, too.
Siiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis!!!
Come, now. Introduce yourself.
Sis, Sissssssssssssss
Siiiiiiiiiiiiiiiis!!!
Burp...
Anya just got heartburn. Hurp.
Oh, dear. Are you all right?
Shall we take a little break
before we start studying?
How have you been lately?
Things must've been pretty hectic at the
Ministry of Foreign Affairs during that summit.
Gathering intel and all.
Huh? Uh, yes...
The Security Service must've realized
that the minister was Twilight.
It was an emergency,
but that was definitely risky.
Is he mocking us for delaying the summit
because of the terrorist attack?!
Don't think you're going to ruin my
reputation in front of Sis, you foul man!
I need to show off!
I need to be on my guard.
A spy versus the Secret Police... So exciting!
Unkie doesn't know Papa's
true identity. Papa wins.
Huff, huff!
Well, you seem rather chipper.
In that case, let's start studying.
I'm probably in the way,
so I'll go shopping.
All right.
Now I have time to take
care of another mission.
But the showdown...
Biology for Good Boys and Girls
Well, let's get started.
I came here reflexively because
Sis asked me to be here,
but why must I bother with
this dopey-faced gremlin?
Okay, try solving this problem.
You get to stay with Sis every day,
you greedy little imp.
I'll throw hard questions at her and
show her how tough society can be!
What?! You got all of them correct?!
Oh, my!
Perhaps you don't need to study.
Oh, no!
I can't cheat on the day of the tests,
so I need to take this seriously.
Th-That was just a fluke.
I just guessed all the answers.
Huh? Uh... Of course you did.
It'd be inconceivable otherwise.
No! That's wrong!
Just how dense are you?
Take this seriously!
I am!
Yuri, please teach her more gently.
I don't want Miss Anya to get expelled.
But I want to go to school...
This was also the wish of my late wife.
Please, Yuri. I'm counting on you. Okay?
Sis
S-S-S-Sis!
O-Okay... But her basic knowledge is just...
Anya will do her bestest!
Anya will become an Imperel Scooter
and become really important
so she can feed Mama lots of yummy things!
What a little angel!
Oh, my!
Where did this angel come from?!
And what in the world is an Imperel Scooter?
Miss Anya, I'll prepare you
some tea snacks right away!
Yay.
She's so considerate of Sis...
No, calm down.
This is the daughter of that vile
sister-stealer! Don't let her fool you!
B-But if this little gremlin happens
to get high marks due to my tutelage,
Sis will say, "I love you, Yuri!"
All right, fine. I'll instruct you.
Come on. You got another one wrong.
No, it's all right.
The important thing is that you
understand why you got it wrong.
Don't think too hard about this.
Just concentrate on this verb.
This takes me back.
Sis, this is how you do this part.
Easy, right?
Ah...
Come on. You can do this.
Do you dislike studying?
It's the worst.
Do you actually like studying, Unkie?
What's wrong with you?
Don't call me "Unkie."
As for me...
I was very frustrated at myself for
being so powerless when I was young.
I wanted to help Sis out as soon as I could.
And to do that, I studied extra hard.
I felt elated every time
I got an answer right,
as if I had grown a centimeter each time.
I worked extra hard in language.
If I was eloquent, I thought I could
become a journalist or a lawyer
and make this world that Sis
lives in an even better place.
I also worked extra hard
in chemistry and biology.
With a strong understanding
of the body and pharmaceuticals,
I thought I could heal any
of Sis's wounds or ailments.
I worked extra hard in mathematics
and physics, as well.
Because I thought that would help my
sister live a stable and easy life.
In the end, I ended up in the
Ministry of Foreign Affairs,
but everything I worked hard to
learn still helps me every day.
Oh...
An ancient wise man once said,
"Knowledge is power."
If you also want to become worthwhile,
you need to unleash your brain's
potential by studying.
No leash is power?!
No!
If I study, I'll be able to make medicine?
That's right.
And make rockets, too?
Of course!
And conquer the world?!
That's, uh... well, sure.
Wait... you want to conquer the world?
All right, bring on your
next set of questions!
Listen well! The test right
before you doesn't matter!
Instead, envision yourself
being successful in the future!
Yes, sir!
Envision Sis's beautiful
smile in that future!
Sir, yes, sir!
Please don't teach her
too many strange ideas.
Well? Have you mastered...
this grammar lesson yet?
What's grammar?
This is a total waste of time!
I'm going home! I can't deal with this crap!
Yuri!
That's right. I need to study, too.
I'm still lacking.
If only I was strong enough,
I could've captured Twilight!
I could've eliminated the
threat from the West!
I need...
more strength to protect
Sis and this country.
Sorry, Sis. I have to go.
Goodness, he's as impatient as ever.
And after I worked so hard making these snacks.
So good... horf!
Aw, he ate all of them.
I guess I'll bake another batch.
It's okay. Anya is full right now.
Back then, if only I could've read
the clock or disarmed the bomb...
I might've been able to properly
help Papa on his mission.
Anya's going to go study in her room.
All right.
My, how commendable.
I'm home.
Welcome home, Loid.
Miss Anya was working
very hard on her studies.
I see. That's great to hear.
Foreign Languages
Easy
Let's take a look...
Hm? Foreign languages?
Yes! She was putting
everything she had into it!
Foreign languages won't be
on her midterms, though.
Heh...
Weeks
Later
Operation Strix may be doomed.
It's finally time, Anya!
How confident are you feeling?
You'll be astonished when you see
that no leash is power, dear Becky.
Huh? What does that even mean?
Anyway, I guess you seem confident.
I can't lose, either!
We will now begin...
your first-term midterm exams!
I did awful in math.
I think I might've gotten
an 80 on my language test.
DAYBREAK
How did the first graders' tests go this time?
I just glanced at the results, and I must
say that they were rather unsavory.
Perhaps the questions were a bit difficult.
Meaning, they were just right.
I'm sure we'll see some parents and guardians
trying to buy their kids'
grades again this year.
Though our current principal
would never allow such things.
Those at the top of this
school will also stand
at the top of this country one day, as well.
Not even a single point can be altered.
These answer sheets are important documents
that will determine the future of this country.
They must be securely locked
away until the grading is done.
My name is Twilight.
I am currently conducting Operation Strix
to maintain peace between the East and West.
But there are currently dark clouds
gathering on this mission's horizon.
The midterms could mean Tonitrus Bolts,
which means that Anya possibly...
No, that she absolutely...
Anya's got this!
She's doomed. There's no doubt about it.
Which means I'll have to rely
on some questionable methods.
I know it's too risky for her
to memorize all the answers
from her entrance exam prep.
Which means that this time, I'll have to
do something more absolute and direct...
and alter her answer sheets
before they're graded!
Goodbye, sir.
The only obstacle is this school's security.
It's not as troublesome as the
management of the entrance exam,
but security is heavy at the
north tower where the safe is.
It will take some time to infiltrate.
I can't do anything too risky and let
the school grow suspicious, either.
I need to be extra careful and
leave no trace that I was here.
Who in the world is that?
He's not one of the instructors, nor any
other member of the faculty I've seen.
More importantly...
He's blatantly suspicious!
My name's Daybreak.
I'm an elite spy for a certain organization.
My mission is to alter a certain
student's answer sheets.
Talk about child's play.
What? How'd I get my cool name?
Apparently, a real super-spy from the West
named Twilight has infiltrated our country,
so I decided I would be the
rising star who'll fight against him.
Twilight of the West, Daybreak of the East.
We'll see which spy comes out on top!
This is my first mission.
Behold! The beginning of a true legend!
He's heading toward the north tower?
Don't tell me he's here for the same reason.
What in the world is all that
nonsensical tumbling?
It's hard to fathom, but he
must be in my line of business.
Not good. If he causes a commotion,
it'll affect my mission, as well.
No, fool! Don't go that way at this time of day!
So, yeah. That teacher was a real hottie.
Security's making their rounds!
Not good!
She's totally into me, too.
Don't even try it. You don't have a prayer.
Like you're one to talk. Just you watch.
I'm gonna get her contact info tomorrow.
Actually, I'll even...
He managed to fool them!
None of this makes sense,
but he managed to fool them!
Is it some form of camouflage?
Such physical strength and courage!
Did he acquire some technique
to overcome his human flaws?
Damn! It's locked!
What should I do?
If he's going to get in the way,
it might be better to eliminate
him before he enters the building,
or while he's busy trying
to unlock the door...
Hello?!
Is he that stupid?!
What if someone notices him?!
Maybe he's a burglar, not a spy?
No, he's far too ill-prepared
for even a burglar.
Leaving any trace of infiltration makes
an inconvenient investigation more likely!
I'll just make it look like some club
got too rowdy during evening practice.
My apologies, soccer club!
The north tower, the north tower...
Damn him... He's just wandering
about completely unguarded.
As much as I'd like to eliminate him, I can't
randomly go after someone I know nothing about.
What in the world is he after?
And can't he be quieter about it?!
Hey, come on, man! No one told
me there'd be someone inside!
It clearly looks like that guard needs
to open the door for me to get in! Hello?!
What should I do? This is the only way in.
Who's there? What are you
doing here at this hour?
Huh? Er, I just had a little
business up ahead.
In the safe? Pardon me,
but are you an instructor?
May I see some ID?
Huh? ID?
Er, uh... Hey, it's me! You know,
the guy from informatics.
I'm famous.
If you do not have ID, please leave.
Aw, don't be like that. Come on,
guy. Just let me in for a bit.
I'm going to call the police.
Shit! If the police show up,
it'll cause even more trouble!
Informatics... Informatics...
Come on, just—huh?
Pardon me.
This was on the floor over there. Is it yours?
Thank goodness I brought
backup IDs for every subject!
Huh? I've never seen that bef—
Ahem... You're the new
instructor, Mister Brown, right?
You'll be able to go in with this.
O-Oh, right, right! I dropped that somewhere.
Thanks, bud.
Not a problem.
He seriously wrote down
mission notes on his hand!
You can't be serious! Is this a trap?!
Is this actually some kind of trap?!
Please, go right on in.
You're a lifesaver.
From what I could read,
there were two student numbers,
and he was altering literature scores.
So he is in my business.
And the two student numbers
belong to the Desmond brothers.
Does that mean his client is...
No, I'm jumping to conclusions.
I lack information.
So here we are... safe number seven.
I totally wrote down the passcode,
because I'm awesome.
WRONG
Wait, did I write down the wrong numbers?
I'm gonna run to the bathroom.
You go right ahead.
Pardon.
There is no public restroom in this building.
More importantly, I don't want to
even think about Operation Strix
being jeopardized over
someone hiring this fool.
Honestly...
Thanks, moron!
I need you to take a little nap.
I'll bring him inside so the
security guard doesn't find him.
Lessee... The first graders' answer sheets...
First graders' answer sheets...
It's probably safer to carry
out my mission after he's done.
Oh, here we go.
His methods sure are crude...
Damn it! This case is locked, too!
Damn it! It won't open!
Come on!
Get on with it...
All right! Mission complete!
That was perfect. I'm quivering
at my own awesomeness.
I've clearly surpassed Twilight
at this point. So sorry, Twilight.
All right! I'm gonna buy me some
beef instead of pork on my way home!
What's this about me? If you're done,
just shut up and leave.
Now my rep's gonna skyrocket,
and I'll get all the jobs!
My name may even make the papers!
Nah, it won't be in the newspapers.
I'm a spy, after all.
No one's ever gonna actually notice me.
All right, then.
While I'm altering these, I'll include
an autograph from Agent Daybreak!
Hey! You're a damn spy! Don't willingly
leave traces that you were here!
Hey... you're awake.
Shit! I couldn't keep myself from yelling
about what an ignoramus he is!
Er, I'm terribly sorry!
I didn't see anything!
I promise I won't tell anyone,
so please, spare my life!
I might just have to take care of him.
Hey, who the hell do you think I am?
You damn well better tell everyone!
Tell them how awesome I am!
Huh?
Hark! My name is Daybreak!
I need you to nonchalantly tell the masses
what an awesome, cool spy I am.
Spread the word far and wide!
I don't mind if you embellish a bit.
For example, how I walked through walls
or stopped a bullet with my bare hands!
Oh, but the details of the
mission are a secret, got it?
TTYL, brother!
Bye, now. Adios!
Who in the world was he?
Are the Desmond brothers' grades
in that much danger, to have a
fool like him take care of them?
It's actually the opposite.
They've been altered to become failing grades.
His client must've been a business rival
or political enemy of Desmond's.
It'd cause problems for me
if they were both expelled.
I'll revert their answers to
what they were originally.
I'll make out what the erased answers
once were and copy their handwriting.
Damn it... That fool gave
me even more work to do.
There, all done.
Looks like both brothers
are quite intelligent.
Especially the older one. He's got
perfect scores in almost every subject.
And on the other hand, we have Anya...
Anya, Anya... Here we go.
This is...
Days
Later
I heard they posted the test
results in the courtyard!
Let's go look!
Lord Damian's rank...
There it is! 11th place overall!
You got 94 in history and
placed second in our grade!
You got a Stella! Brilliant, Lord Damian!
Congratulations!
Ugh. I'm in 46th place.
I guess that's not too bad, though.
I don't see your name, Anya.
I wonder where you placed.
You should probably start at the bottom.
I actually already know where I placed.
Papa said in his mind that he went to check.
I found you, Anya!
213th...
D-Don't worry about it too much,
Anya. Better luck next time.
G-Good for you, I guess.
You apparently didn't fail.
I can't even laugh. Let's go.
Yes. Anya didn't get a single Tonitrus Bolt!
Heh.
Well done!
Now Papa's mission will be somewhat safer.
Good girl.
Wow... Even with that rank, she's smiling.
You're so positive, Anya!
That's wonderful!
Papa! I worked hard on my tests!
You just barely avoided failing all
of them. How can you be so proud?
This isn't how it went in my head.
I need to be even stricter
before her next midterms!
That's amazing, Miss Anya!
All your scores added together
exceed 100 points!
Then again, she managed to avoid
failing all of her tests on her own,
which was unexpected.
I guess she is working hard
to do the best she can.
Because of that, my mission's safe for now.
I guess I should thank her.
What's that smirk for? Why aren't
you reflecting on your mistakes?
Stella Needed to Become an Imperial Scholar: 7
Tonitrus Bolts until Expulsion: 7
Knowledge: +5
We're going to review after dinner.
Shock!
What? The mission failed?
No way! I totally—
I'm fired?! Hey, wait!
Hey! But my legend has just begun!
A REVENGE PLOT AGAINST DESMOND
MAMA BECOMES THE WIND